evannex.com 2015-11-27

# Privacy Policy, Aftermarket Tesla Accessories, Gear, parts for Model S | EVANNEX Aftermarket Tesla Accessories

**Online Privacy Policy**

The following Privacy Policy applies only to the EVannex™ web site and information provided by you or otherwise collected online by EVannex™. 

We are concerned about privacy

Your privacy is very important to us. EVannex™ (“we” or “us”) respects and protects the privacy of its visitors.  In this document, we explain how we use the information you supply to us.  If we update our privacy policy, all revisions will be posted on this page. We reserve the right to change the privacy policy at any time. 

Information collection and use

Two types of information may be collected when you visit our web site:  (i) information that you knowingly provide us (called personally identifiable information); and (ii) information that is obtained from your visit but is not directly associated with you (called non-personally identifiable information). 

Personally identifiable information

Personally identifiable information may include information that you provide to us by requesting information, when registering for special offers or programs or when you purchase products online.  This may include your name, address (including billing and shipping addresses), telephone number, e-mail address, organization, city, state and zip code.  We may use this information to process and ship orders, to contact you about the status of your order, to contact you with answers to your questions, or to provide information about new and exciting products, services, promotions and corporate-related information.  We may use mailings, telephone calls and e-mail to contact you. 

You also may create an account through EVannex™ at any time by providing your email address and creating a unique password.  An account is not required to visit our site or to place an order through teslaccessories.com.  Creating an account allows you to save order information, order history, track the status of your orders and set your ordering preferences.  For your privacy and security, we do not store credit card numbers in your account. You may change saved account information at any time. 

When purchasing products from us online, additional personally identifiable information, such as credit card information, will be collected.  This information is collected in order to process your order. 

We are committed to the protection of the privacy of our customers and visitors.  While in the checkout process of our online store, we make use of 128 bit SSL encryption via digital IDs provided and certified PCI Compliant/Shopify Secure. These IDs enable our commerce site to conduct authenticated, strongly encrypted online commerce.  Customers can submit credit card numbers or other personal information to our site with the assurance that they are doing business with us (not an impostor's "spoof" of our site) and that the information which they are sending to us cannot be intercepted or decrypted by anyone else. 

Requesting removal of your information

If you have registered for special e-mail offerings, you may unsubscribe from the program by visiting the e-mail unsubscribe page or click on the links available at the bottom of any of these special offer e-mails.  You may also request the removal of your information by contacting us via e-mail. 

Non-personally identifiable information

Non-personally identifiable information is collected without any direct association with you specifically. In the normal course of using this website, we may collect information about your habits and usage of our sites. 

Our web site may contain technologies known as action tags, web beacons or 1x1 pixel gifs. These employ a common internet technique used to compile aggregated statistics about the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns, common navigation paths within the site, types of browsers and platforms that access the site and the average connection speeds used to connect to the site. This information is used to enhance the online experience of our customers. These technologies do not use or collect personally identifiable information, such as names or address, and do not link online actions to an identifiable person. 

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using the Internet. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregated information and to audit the use of our site.  If we are required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, we will provide these IP addresses to the proper authorities. 

Information sharing and disclosure

Agents, employees and contractors of EVannex™ who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the high standards of our company.

Information about you specifically will not be used for any purpose other than to carry out the services you requested from us. 

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone at any time.

We will not use any personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us in delivering to you the services you have requested.

We may send personally identifiable information about you to other organizations when:

(i)                 We have your consent to share the information (you will be provided the opportunity to opt-out if you desire).  For example, if you opt-in for emails we will share this information with our marketing provider.

(ii)               We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested.  For example, we need to share information with credit card providers and shippers to bill and ship the product you requested. 

(iii)             We are required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena.

Use of Cookies and Applets

Cookies and applets are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our servers to identify your computer.  Cookies and applets are only read by the domain that placed them there and are unable to execute any code or virus.  We may use cookies or applets to recognize you when you visit our sites, to personalize your experience and generally to serve you better.  We do not use cookies or applets to track your activities once you leave our web site. 

You may delete these files from your computer at any time.  You can set your web browser to notify you if such information is about to be placed on your computer, and you can choose the option in your web browser to refuse it.  If you refuse the information, you may not be able to make full use of the features on our web site. 

Links to and from our web site

Our web site may contain links to and from other web sites that are not operated or controlled by us.  WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF WEB SITES THAT WE DO NOT OPERATE, and our privacy policy does not apply to these sites. 

How changes to the privacy policy will be communicated

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our web site for 30 days.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should [contact us](http://www.teslaccessories.com/pages/contact-us "Contact Us").
